# anna foster dolan

720.272.0069 anna.dolan@gmail.com

# summary

I am a software developer with a penchant for problem-solving and an eye for detail. My experience is primarily in Ruby, and I am continually working to add languages to my repertoire and become a stronger developer. With my background as a real-estate professional, I am skilled in time management and organization, and I have a great deal of experience in a client-facing environment. My skills are suited for a broad range of industries, and I hope to work alongside, and learn from, a team of well-rounded developers.

# skills

Languages: Ruby, HTML, CSS, SQL, Javascript Testing: Minitest, Capybara, RSpec, VCR,

Selenium Webdriver

Frameworks: Sinatra, Rails

**Tools:** Atom, Bootstrap, Sass, jQuery, Faraday **Other:** API consumption & design, Git, Agile

workflow, Pivotal Tracker

# projects

## Pinspiration (Github) (Launch)

Pinspiration is a clone of Pinterest that also serves a JSON API for comments on pins. I worked on this project with Erin Pintozzi, Jon Kimble, and Vido Seaver.

#### Root & Branch (Github) (Launch)

This app is a mock store called Root & Branch. It is a fully functioning web store written in Rails, complete with user authentication and admin authorization, a functioning cart and checkout, and Bootstrap styling. This was a group project with Erin Pintozzi, Megan Talbot and Ali Schlereth.

#### It Takes a Village (Github) (Launch)

(Work in progress) This project is for a client who wants to create an app to allow new parents to request help from their community. This Rails app incorporates Google maps, uses Paperclip with AWS for image upload, and is styled with Bootstrap 3, HTML, CSS, Sass, and some JQuery. We used Twilio for password reset. I worked with Megan Talbot on this project.

# experience

2016-2017 Backend Engineering Student, Turing School, Denver, CO

## 2011-2016 Assistant Investment Manager, Triton Properties, Denver, CO

- Assisted in managing more than 250 apartment units in 9 buildings
- Interviewed, trained and supervised leasing agents
- Tracked vacancy, renewals, pricing, and other statistics and reported to property owners

## 2010-2011, Keyholder, American Apparel, Denver, CO

- Consistently achieved and exceeded daily sales goals
- Supervised and trained sales associates

#### education

University of Colorado Denver, Denver, CO
BA Drawing